OF COURSE I'VE PLAYED
WITH FEET BEFORE
YEAH, I LOVE FEET
(WOMEN TALKING ON PHONES)
♪ ♪
♪ YOU USED TO CALL ME ON MY,
YOU USED TO, YOU USED TO ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ YOU USED TO CALL ME
ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ CALL ME ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ AND I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY MEAN
ONE THING ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ EVER SINCE I LEFT
THE CITY YOU ♪
♪ GOT A REPUTATION
FOR YOURSELF NOW ♪
♪ EVERYBODY KNOWS
AND I FEEL LEFT OUT ♪
♪ GIRL YOU GOT ME DOWN,
YOU GOT ME STRESSED OUT ♪
♪ CAUSE EVER SINCE I
LEFT THE CITY, YOU ♪
♪ STARTED WEARING LESS
AND GOIN' OUT MORE ♪
♪ GLASSES OF CHAMPAGNE
OUT ON THE DANCE FLOOR ♪
♪ HANGIN' WITH SOME GIRLS
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE ♪
♪ YOU USED TO CALL ME
ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ CALL ME ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ EVER SINCE I LEFT THE
CITY, YOU, YOU, YOU ♪
♪ YOU AND ME WE JUST
DON'T GET ALONG ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I DID YOU WRONG ♪
♪ GOING PLACES WHERE
YOU DON'T BELONG ♪
♪ EVER SINCE I LEFT
THE CITY, YOU ♪
♪ YOU GOT EXACTLY
WHAT YOU ASKED FOR ♪
♪ RUNNING OUT OF PAGES IN YOUR
PASSPORT ♪
♪ HANGING WITH SOME GIRLS
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE ♪
♪ YOU USED TO CALL ME
ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ CALL ME ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ THESE DAYS, ALL I DO IS ♪
♪ WONDER IF YOU BENDIN' OVER
BACKWARDS FOR SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ WONDER IF YOUR ROLLIN'
BACKWOODS FOR SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ DOING THINGS I
TAUGHT YOU GETTIN' NASTY
FOR SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ YOU DON'T NEED
NO ONE ELSE ♪
NOBODY ELSE, NO ♪
♪ WHY YOU NEVER ALONE ♪
♪ WHY YOU ALWAYS
TOUCHING ROAD ♪
♪ USED TO ALWAYS STAY AT
HOME, BE A GOOD GIRL ♪
♪ YOU WAS IN THE ZONE ♪
♪ YOU SHOULD JUST
BE YOURSELF ♪
♪ RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE
SOMEONE ELSE ♪
♪ YOU USED TO CALL ME
ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ CALL ME ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ LATE NIGHT WHEN
YOU NEED MY LOVE ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ I KNOW WHEN
THAT HOTLINE BLING ♪
♪ THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING ♪
♪ EVER SINCE I
LEFT THE CITY ♪
♪ ♪